Like the Prophet Sallallahu
Alaihi Wasallam encouraged
us to make a lot of dua
in our sujood.
In fact he said,
It is most very likely that
you
will be granted your request.
You now want to make dua in
your sujood. You make the
dua.
If it is Sallallahu Alaihi
Nabi that
you want to make,
you make Sallallahu Alaihi
Nabi.
You know that is upon your
choice
now that you are making dua
in
your sujood.
What may become an innovation
is that
you are doing that in the
last
sujood.
And every day it's the last
So that it becomes as if the
last sujood is a sujood for
extra
dua.
Don't do it like that.
Don't particularize what the
Sharia generalizes.
You can make your dua in any
of the sujood.
Now don't make it become as
if
the only time you can make
your
dua a sujood is when you are
upon the last sujood.
But if you want to make dua
in sujood, you can make
Sallallahu Alaihi
Nabi.
If you want to make dua in
all the eight sujood of a
four
raka'ah Sallah, yes you can
make Sallahu
Alaihi Nabi.
Don't forget that is if you
are
praying alone or you are
leading the
people in prayer.